psoug.org 2018-12-28

# Oracle PL/SQL Database Code Library and Resources | Examples | Packages | Syntax | PL/SQL | SQL |

## Privacy Policy

PSOUG.org has adopted the following privacy policy as part of our commitment to protect any personal information which you may provide to us through this website or by any other means. 

Any change to this privacy policy will be posted on this website and will become effective 5 days after posting. Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to other websites linked through this website. Personal information which you choose to provide to other websites will be subject to the privacy policies of those websites. 

  1. **General**  
We will not use or disclose your personal information unless you have given your permission, except for the following purposes: 
    * to assess, operate and improve this website and the services provided through it; 
    * to keep you informed about us and our sevices about this website; 
    * if we are required to disclose such Personal Information by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
  2. **Transfer of Personal Information**  
We will not sell, trade or rent your Personal Information to others unless you have given your permission. We will follow the relevant legal requirements and use all reasonable precautions to ensure that only responsible third parties see your Personal Information. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or act or omission of third parties who receive the Personal Information. 
  3. **Third Parties**  
In addition to the use of your Personal Information as described above, we may also gather anonymous information which may be used by us or shared with third parties. This is information which does not identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving this website or the services provided through it. 
  4. **Cookies**  
This website may, from time to time, use Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes and they can make the World Wide Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of Cookies is normal practice in the industry and are typically used to help tailor a site's features for their customers. Cookies do not personally identify users but they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initally set to accept Cookies. If you prefer, you can set your Internet browser to refuse Cookies. if your Internet browser refuses Cookies, some parts of this site may not be accessible to you. 
  5. **Terms of Service**  
Please review our Terms of Service, which also governs your use of this site. 
  6. **Passwords**  
For your security, password-protected accounts are required to use certain parts of the system. 
  7. **Email Addresses**  
We will not sell, lease, give, or transfer email addresses or other personal information from our users to any other business or entity. Your email address is safe with us. 
  8. **Information security**   
Although we have implemented appropriate business procedures to maintain information in a secure manner, due to the nature of the Internet as well as forces beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of data on the PSOUG.org site.
